Hi everyone, welcome to another leggings video. You know, I love black. Black is my happy color, but sometimes
there are occasions to wear different colors. So I'm going to show you some colorful leggings today
from Slick Cheek and I hope you're going to like them because I think they're really cool.
So first of all, the one I'm wearing is a Slinky Styles leggings. It's, I think, one of the
news models. It has a different cut than these ones and it has a anti front
contouring cut which I really like and super comfortable so I wanted to show
this one to you as well. To be honest I thought I was going to do a slinky
styles video but then I realized that these are all sleek cheek and the
companies are like sister companies and I thought that the light stretchy
fabrics are sleek cheek and the more firm ones let alone PVC ones are slinky
styles but apparently I'm wrong and I have no idea why these are sleek cheek. As much
as I love black I really think that these metallic colors are super cool
that's why even I am going to wear them. I don't know if these colors are unique
but I have not seen such cool colors so far and the material is like a yeah
thick pee not that shiny PVC bit stretchy and really comfortable so I'm
going to switch into one now so this color is called rust metallic and it's
really cool color there's a difference between this one and the other two this
This one has no seam in the back of the leg as the knees have.
And here the waistband is not as wide as with these pants.
So a bit different.
I think they're called different as well.
I'm going to write it down for you.
Anyway I like this color compared with black a lot.
Okay, let's continue with the blue ones.
That was easy, but in fact, it's not that easy.
It's kind of a struggle to get into these because they're really tight and the waistband is not that stretchy.
But I always think of that cat meme because once you got into them, they really do fit really good.
to be honest I prefer this model with the waistband that's more wide and the seam here
because I think it makes a nicer shape between the hip and the waist if the waistband is
going higher but that's just my preference and I prefer the blue color over the rusty red one
but I think this one's going to be my favorite. I combined the blue leggings with bright red shoes.
Do you think that's too much or is it okay? I think it's a bit too bold for my taste at least
and now I'm going to switch into metallic plum.
Okay so that's definitely my favorite color. It's not black but it is also not too bright
It was easier to get into it than the blue one.
I don't know, I think it's because I've worn this more often.
I can tell you that the more you wear these leggings, the better they're going to fit
and the easier you're going to get into them.
I really like this look as a whole with the shoes, the top and the choker here.
I think that's a cool outfit to, I don't know, have a stroll in the city or some summer day
beach club when there's going to be a beach club open again I don't know.
Okay I think we're done I showed you some cool alternatives to black leggings.
Tell me in the comments which one is your favorite and don't forget to subscribe to my channel.
Have a nice day see you around!
Thanks for watching!